<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mount Manager</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="pref_previously_started">prev_start</string>
    <string name="fr_warning">Warning!</string>
    <string name="fr_text">Make sure you know what you\'re doing! I am not responsible for bricked devices, dead SD cards, thermonuclear war, or you getting fired because the alarm app failed. Please do some research if you don\'t know how linux filesystems work! YOU are choosing to run this app, and if you point the finger at me for messing up your device, I will laugh at you. This app requires a rooted device if you want to utilize the rw/ro toggle feature.</string>
    <string name="okay">Okay</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fs_detail_view">FsDetailViewActivity</string>
    <string name="yeah">Yes</string>
    <string name="nope">No</string>
    <string name="fr_error">Error</string>
    <string name="fr_noroot">Something sinister prevented listing the filesystems. Did you allow root access back there? If not, please do that. If your device is not rooted, do that first.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_filesystem_detail">Filesystem Details</string>
    <string name="yousurebruh">!!!WARNING!!!</string>
    <string name="moresure">"Are you really sure you want to perform the following action: Remount "</string>
    <string name="as">" as "</string>
    <string name="readonly">" read-only (Mount option: ro). It is currently mounted as read-write (rw)"</string>
    <string name="readwrite">" read-write (Mount option: rw). It is currently mounted as read-only (rw)"</string>
    <string name="ohno">Cancel</string>
    <string name="title_activity_filesystem_remount">FilesystemRemount</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="cont">Continue</string>
    <string name="swipe_to_confirm_action">Swipe to Confirm Action</string>
    <string name="remountfs">Remount filesystem</string>
    <string name="button">Button</string>
    <string name="wasremounted">"Filesystem was remounted: "</string>
    <string name="filesystem_being_remounted">Filesystem being remounted:</string>
    <string name="filesystem_remounting">Remounting Filesystem</string>
    <string name="warnin_boi">Warning!</string>
    <string name="nukewars">"The filesystem you are trying to remount is not on our list of things people normally remount. This might just be us being your mom, but if you are not sure, you probably shouldn't do this. Actually, if you're not 420% sure you know what you're doing, PRESS THAT BACK BUTTON RIGHT NOW. Your phone could crash. Your phone could get bricked. You could get sued. Kittens might die. A climate change denier might become president of the USA. Oh shit that last part ALREADY HAPPENED, and if you do this without knowing, it would have been your fault. So there. "</string>
    <string name="toro">From read-write to read-only</string>
    <string name="torw">From read-only to read-write</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About</string>
    <string name="abouttext">
        <![CDATA[
<h1>Mount Manager</h1>
<h5>Version BUILD_VERSION</h5>
<h3>By Aditya Goturu</h3>
<p><i>Remount filesystems as read-write or read-only.</i></p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/aditya3098/mountmanager">https://github.com/aditya3098/mountmanager</a></p>
<h4>Contact:</h4>
<p><a href="mailto:aditya@sudoforlunch.org">aditya@sudoforlunch.org</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.sudoforlunch.org/">https://www.sudoforlunch.org/</a> (I really should update this more)</p>
<h4>License:</h4>

This is free and unencumbered software released into the public domain.

Anyone is free to copy, modify, publish, use, compile, sell, or
distribute this software, either in source code form or as a compiled
binary, for any purpose, commercial or non-commercial, and by any
means.

In jurisdictions that recognize copyright laws, the author or authors
of this software dedicate any and all copyright interest in the
software to the public domain. We make this dedication for the benefit
of the public at large and to the detriment of our heirs and
successors. We intend this dedication to be an overt act of
relinquishment in perpetuity of all present and future rights to this
software under copyright law.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND,
EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF
MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT.
IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR
OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE,
ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR
OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.

For more information, please refer to &lt;http://unlicense.org/&gt;

 ]]>
    </string>


</resources>
